twobillsdrive.com 2006-06-19

# Two Bills Drive: Buffalo Bills News

**Privacy Policy**  

* * *

**by TBD Staff**  
TBD Featured Columnist  
July 11, 2001 

* * *

Privacy Policy  
Depending on what you do when you visit any Web site, you are providing information about your visit to the site's owners. This includes Two Bills Drive. We value privacy and think you do too, so we want you to have the information you need to make your own decisions about your personal privacy. When you visit or supply information to any Web site, we think it's a good idea for you to first understand what that site's privacy policies are. If the site doesn't tell you, don't hesitate to ask. 

The bottom line at Two Bills Drive is that we use the information that we get from your visit for internal tracking purposes, to make Two Bills Drive as useful and interesting to you as we can, and to respond to your requests for information or other services. Except as specifically noted below, we do not use your personal information for any other purpose, we never sell it to any third party, and we never even share it with any third party. 

Here is more detail on how we handle information we learn from you when you visit Two Bills Drive. 

Browsing:  
When you visit Two Bills Drive and move from page to page, read pages, or download content onto your computer, we learn which pages are visited, what is downloaded, the domains our visitors come from (e.g. 'aol.com,' or 'nrc.pair.com') and the addresses of sites visited immediately before coming to our site. However, none of this is associated with you as an individual. It is measured only in aggregate. Two Bills Drive uses cookie technology as part of our login procedures for some content and our message forums. The information in the cookies lets us store your login information so you do not have to enter it many times during your session. These cookies do not capture your email address or other personal information, and cannot be read by any site other than Two Bills Drive. 

We also use standard web server log files, to help us count visitors and evaluate our site's technical capacity. We use this information to find out how many people visit Two Bills Drive, help us arrange the pages in the most user-friendly way, keep the site browser-friendly, and to make our pages more useful to our visitors. We record information on site traffic for advertising purposes, but not information on individual visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular will be kept or used. 

Email:  
When you send us an email to comment on something or ask us a question, we learn your exact email address and the thoughts you share. 

We use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we sometimes store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. 

Advertisers:  
Two Bills Drive utilizes banner ads and other advertisements that are purchased by various companies. We supply these companies with information on Two Bills Drive' traffic and other general demographic information on our readers, but we provide this information in aggregate, and DO NOT give them any of our subscriber or registration information. Again, any information you enter in a registration form or other information is protected by this privacy policy, and we WILL NOT give this information to anyone. 

Legal Stuff  
In certain extreme situations (seldom, but they could happen), Two Bills Drive may be forced to release your personal information to judges, police, other law enforcement personnel, or other officers of a court or other legal authority. By subscribing to our services, you agree that Two Bills Drive is in no way liable for any result of the release of this information.
